Thank you for watching!
Kettle and Idol
Q. All-out performance
And second, zenryoku performance.
All-out performance.
Can I ask you about this?
What do I always keep in mind when I perform?
Even if my hair or makeup is messed up,
Even if my hair or makeup is messed up, even if it gets all over my face,
Even if my hair or makeup gets messed up, even if it gets all over my face, I just give it my all.
I see.
So you are saying that you show the whole of your feelings in your performance, is that correct?
I love both singing and dancing,
I love both singing and dancing, but when it comes to whether I can say that I am good at it, I am not so sure,
I still think that I am not so good at both singing and dancing,
However, when I give my all in a live performance, people say that I am good at it,
But when I give my all in a live performance, I am often told how good I look,
I myself love idols who give their all in their performances.
I myself love idols who give their best,
I see idols who are performing the way I like to perform,
I wish I could do something like that,
I always give my best to everyone.
But I also want people to see how cute I am because I am a girl, and I want people to see how hostile I am.
I want to convey more than that.
At first, I would say, "Your face looks good today,
I think my hair looks good today.
My hair looks good today,
I thought, "I'm going to look pretty today," and then I went on stage,
But all those feelings were blown away,
But all those feelings were blown away at the end. I was like, "Did I look like this? I wanted to perform live,
I would love to perform live.
I would love to perform live. It's the best live performance.
It's so much hotter than the video.
Hot air?
Pressure.
Oh, it comes from that stage.
It's the most obvious.
But it's a good word, isn't it?
I don't hear "hot air" that often.
It's been a long time.
I really hear "hot wind.
Yes.
Yes, I have.
You don't even hear about it in the electricity forecast.
Our hot air.
Look at our pressure.
By all means.
Take a look.
You are sweating.
We are sweating.
And the audience is sweating, too,
You are sweating too, right?
It really is.
The sense of unity is wonderful.
I'm looking forward to seeing the show.
We will face off.
I'm a little bit tired too.
All of the members of the women's color group eat quite a bit.
This show is
Mr. TOTALLY
Yudai-kun
××xx and xx by kotobatten
Thank you very much for providing this program!
Thank you very much!